He advised Sudip ji to buy Tata Steel.
So it is better that there is preparation for
big action in the metal space and steel space.
But action is
also happening in our quarterly results space.
Now ICICI PSE numbers are going to come tomorrow.
Now what is expected from the results of this company
?  Let us know
from Pooja.  Tell Pooja.  ICICI PDL results may be good.
If we look at the gross premium income, there is a
growth of 11% there.
Although there will be a decline in profits,
VNB margin is expected to increase from 21% to around 23%
and the new business app
i.e. premium app can see a growth of around 6.5%.
So the results will be
good overall.  The growth of non-linked business will be
quite good.
Improvement in product mix will also be beneficial here.  The
protection business
is expected to recover and
VNB
margins may also see an increase due to increased share of ULIPs.  There were
plans to make some changes in the product mix for quite some time.  Now
what guidance does it give for the future?
We will keep an eye on all these things.  So
overall good numbers are expected
from ICICI Piden.  All right.  Although before the numbers
we are seeing it trying to recover a bit
but it is seen trading in a sluggish small range.
Sir
what is your opinion about this ICICI proof before the number?
Yes, absolutely Neha, if we talk about ICICI potential, in
fact I have given this call on it.
So the expectations
are positive but I think there will be some nervousness before the numbers are announced.
So there is an important
stop loss which has to be maintained and that
is at the level of 660.
I don't think there is any problem unless it goes below 660.
So just wait and watch
with a stop loss of 660. If the numbers are good then
we can see levels up to 740 in this counter.
Okay, so this is my opinion.